<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Minimal Blog</title><description>A minimalistic blog built with Astro</description><link>https://example.com/</link><language>en-us</language><item><title>5 tips to master dataflows in Power Platform</title><link>https://example.com/posts/5-tips-to-master-dataflows-in-power-platform/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://example.com/posts/5-tips-to-master-dataflows-in-power-platform/</guid><description>Dataflows are a great tool to learn in Power Platform. They feel often forgotten, but are a fantastic way to bring data in to Dataverse solutions and transform and shape the data before it reaches your table.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 Feb 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>ALM Accelerator Part 1: An introduction</title><link>https://example.com/posts/alm-accelerator-part-1-an-introduction/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://example.com/posts/alm-accelerator-part-1-an-introduction/</guid><description>Welcome to a new series of posts where I look to provide an overview and in-depth guide on the ALM Accelerator. In Part 1, I want to run through what the ALM Accelerator is, how it can be used, and when to consider using it in your Power Platform development.</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Creating visual hierarchies in model-driven apps</title><link>https://example.com/posts/creating-visual-hierarchies-in-model-driven-apps/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://example.com/posts/creating-visual-hierarchies-in-model-driven-apps/</guid><description>Sometimes model-driven apps can be considered quite boring due to their predictability in how the interface is presented. Personally I love the interface and the simplicity it can offer(if configured correctly!). Adding visual elements to your model-driven apps can greatly enhance the user experience and improve adoption.</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Field validation in canvas apps/custom pages</title><link>https://example.com/posts/field-validation-in-canvas-apps/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://example.com/posts/field-validation-in-canvas-apps/</guid><description>In this post, I want to run through how to do field validation in Power Apps canvas apps/custom pages, and the different options that are available. The ultimate goal is to provide the best user experience when validating fields, and what to watch out for.</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Getting Started with Astro</title><link>https://example.com/posts/getting-started/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://example.com/posts/getting-started/</guid><description>A quick introduction to the Astro web framework and why it&apos;s great for content-focused sites.</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Pass multiple record Id&apos;s to a custom page from the command bar</title><link>https://example.com/posts/pass-multiple-record-ids-to-a-custom-page-from-the-command-bar/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://example.com/posts/pass-multiple-record-ids-to-a-custom-page-from-the-command-bar/</guid><description>Opening a custom page from the command bar opens up model-driven apps to some amazing possibilities. This convergence of apps is something I am particularly fond of and excited to see what else can be done to combine the best of the Canvas App and Model-Driven sides of the coin.</description><pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>